[theme music playing]
I've prepared something for both of you.
A prenuptial agreement that both
of you will sign, of course.
It says there that should you
and Arnaldo decide to separate,
one hundred percent of your assets
will go to Arnaldo.
[Ivy] No amount of money can
ever compare to my love for you.
[Camia] I promised Lily
that I would trust her plan.
But I can't allow those greedy
Ardientes to do this to her.
[Ivy] After the wedding,
we should prioritize
securing Arnaldo's victory
in the elections.
Now, you're talking like a true Ardiente.
You should run for office.
[Ivy] What about Emilia?
Won't she be running
for a position like before?
Excuse me.
[Emilia] Remember,
you're just a wife-to-be.
I'm the mother.
So, that means I will still be
the Queen of Ardiente.
Your actions will only
get you into trouble!
[Emilia] I'd rather do it myself.
That way, I'll take her life
with my own, two hands--
[Claire] Then you'd better
do it successfully, Emilia!
We have a teaching drive
in Barangay Siete.
Maybe you'd like to come?
[Diego] Of course.
We'll bring more help
for the kids there too.
[Emilia] I'm throwing a bridal shower
for my future daughter-in-law.
Maybe you can let me borrow
some of your macho men
to entertain
my daughter-in-law, Ivy Aguas.
For his marriage, for his success…
Viva Ardiente!
[in unison] Viva Ardiente!
[Ivy] Is this part of your plan, Emilia?
Okay. Let's have fun!
-[water splashing]
-[women exclaim]
[Emilia] Let's go get a drink.
Oh, thank you, Emilia, but… I'm good.
Come on. Don't be such a party pooper.
-Have a drink.
-You have it. Thank you.
Come on, just a sip.
[Emilia] You poisoned me!
You poisoned yourself.
This particular poison
is one of the worst.
Your throat will constrict so tight.
[Claire] You have to throw up!
You have to throw up, Emilia!
Spit out the poison! Do it! Hurry!
-No, no, no, no.
-Mayor.
Just let me explain.
-This isn't part of the deal. Mayor.
-No, I just wanna be with you.
I just wanna be with--
You're so sexy.
[high-pitched ringing]
Ivy, I've been waiting for this.
I've waited for this
for so long. Oh, my gosh.
Stay there, stay there.
-Mayor…
-Stay there.
You're very beautiful, Ivy.
Ivy Aguas. I just want to talk to you.
This isn't part of the deal.
Ivy, come on. I've waited
for this for so long!
I'm begging you. Please give it to me.
I want you. I need you!
-We'll finally be together.
-Mayor.
No, no, no! Don't you want this?
-You do, don't you? You want this, right?
-I didn't agree to this!
You want this. You keep saying no.
I give you everything you want.
Why can't you give me what I want? Huh?
Why are you giving me a hard time?
Mayor, I'm not Ivy!
What are you talking about?! Huh?!
I love you. Give it to me.
[woman sobbing]
[woman screaming] No, Mayor!
-Why do you keep saying no?!
-[sobbing continues, screams]
Why do you keep saying no? Huh?!
Is it because of Diego?! Huh?!
For him to take my place?!
I give you everything!
And then, you're still refusing?
We're getting married!
Ivy, we're getting married.
We're getting married.
-Mayor, I'm not Ivy.
-I'm gonna take care of you.
I'm gonna take care of you.
-Mayor, I didn't agree to this.
-I'm gonna make you happy.
I'm gonna make you happy.
I'm gonna love you.
I'm gonna give you everything
that you need.
And I'm gonna do anything that I want
because you're mine!
I'm yours and you're mine! You're mine!
[woman] Let me go! [sobbing]
[retches]
-You have to throw up!
-Guys! Guys, I'm just joking!
Of course, I wouldn't poison
my future mother-in-law.
I didn't put poison in this!
[chuckles]
I'd rather get married than mourn.
Don't overshadow my moment.
You mean, there's no poison
in that thing? Huh?
None! I didn't poison you.
Gosh, Emilia!
You really made
my bridal shower memorable.
I really had so much fun,
just like you said I would.
[breathing heavily]
And I did tell you, Emilia…
Don't try me.
-[vial clatters]
-[shudders]
[labored breathing]
-Emilia?
-I can't breathe.
What?! Hold on.
Emilia! Emilia! Hey! Emilia! Help!
Somebody help us! Please! Emilia! Emilia!
Emilia! Help!
Wait for me here!
[suspenseful music playing]
[woman] Mayor! [sobbing]
[Arnaldo] I said stop! Stop!
Don't you hear me?! I love you!
-[suspenseful action music]
-[Arnaldo] I love you!
There's nothing you can do!
-You are mine! You are mine!
-[woman, sobbing] Mayor!
-Mayor!
-[Arnaldo] You are mine.
[woman] Mayor. [sobbing]
I'm sorry. Ivy, I'm sorry.
-[Arnaldo shushes]
-[sobbing]
[Arnaldo] Let's make things clear.
You're mine, right?
You're mine. I'm yours.
No matter what happens, I'm yours.
I'm yours.
-[woman] Mayor!
-[Arnaldo] You're mine!
-You're all mine!
-[sobbing continues]
You're all mine!
-Huh?!
-[woman] Mayor!
You're all mine!
Come on. Please.
Let's make some babies! I want 12 babies.
Twelve little Arnaldos.
Little Ardientes everywhere.
Our house will be--
Reporting for duty, Mayor.
[tense music playing]
[exhales sharply]
I like these calm, little
moments before the storm.
[exhales sharply]
Madrigal!
[suspenseful action music playing]
Long time no see.
Nice suit.
Just like old times, Mayor.
The only difference
is that I work for Jaguar now.
[breathes deeply]
He wants me to tell you
that your days are numbered.
[suspenseful music playing]
I should've killed you back then.
You should've.
[gunshots]
[suspenseful music playing]
-What was that?!
-[man] Where did that come from?
-Hey!
Secure Arnaldo, hurry!
[suspenseful music playing]
[gunshots]
-Come on! Take that! And that!
-[gunshots]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Arnaldo grunts]
[gunshot]
[gunshots]
[Arnaldo] Go after him! Go! Hurry!
[suspenseful music playing]
Mayor, he's gone! He got away!
[Arnaldo grunts]
Give me your gun!
Come on!
[Claire] Emilia? We're here!
Emi--
Emilia?
[suspenseful music playing]
EMILIA'S WITH ME. DON'T WORRY,
I WON'T HURT HER.
EMILIA'S WITH ME.
DON'T WORRY, I WON'T HURT HER.
JAGUAR
[mysterious music playing]
Where am I?
How did I get here?
Jaguar?
[suspenseful music playing]
Arnaldo! What happened?!
Did you fire shots?!
Yes, I did! Madrigal was here!
He now works for Jaguar!
And he almost killed me!
What?!
Madrigal now works for Jaguar?!
Yes!
That son of a--!
Those bastards!
I am going to kill them all!
I will kill them all!
[unsettling music playing]
Why did you bring me here?
[beeps]
[in distorted voice] I saved you.
I felt sorry for you.
You were like a withered flower
when I brought you here.
I want to take care of you, Emilia.
I don't need anyone to do that for me.
I can take care of myself.
I'm a strong woman.
[chuckles]
Not exactly, Emilia.
You're just being manipulated
by the people around you.
You've become weak.
That's not true.
Everything is under my control.
Emilia, if you thought
you were strong before,
well you aren't anymore.
You've neglected yourself.
You're weak now.
That's not true!
Where's your husband?
-He's not even looking for you,
-That's not true.
or calling to know how you're doing.
Meanwhile, your father and your son
[chuckles]
are both enjoying themselves
at a stag party.
They don't care about you, Emilia.
[crying] That's not true.
[chuckles]
That's not true!
I'm strong. I can take care of myself.
[dark dramatic music playing]
Don't worry, Emilia.
You'll regain your strength.
Believe me.
Emilia…
I want to lay my love on you.
[tense music playing]
[exhales sharply]
[grunts]
[tense music playing]
[Jepoy] You got lucky tonight, Arnaldo.
But your time will come.
Okay.
Stand watch outside.
Secure the entire area.
Jaguar could attack anytime. Do it now.
-Yes, Mayor.
-Now, hurry!
[Arnaldo exhales sharply]
Screw that bastard Jaguar.
That son of a gun is becoming
a threat to the coming wedding.
That's right.
[stammers] So, what's the plan?
The plan is…
we'll do everything to stop that animal.
Okay. Okay.
[Julio] Come to think of it.
I think you should have
your mother picked up,
as well as Ivy Aguas.
I'm sure he plans
to attack those two as well.
Okay, Grandpa. I'll go pick them up.
No, no, no, no, no!
Arnaldo, you stay here.
If Emilia's and Ivy's lives are in danger,
you're in twice the danger.
Truth of the matter is,
I would rather Emilia
and Ivy die than you.
You're far too important to me.
We'll just send your bodyguards
to pick them up.
Those kids were so inspiring.
Diego… It's nice, isn't it?
We really felt the strong
support of the people there.
Take a seat.
She's right.
Those Ardientes won't be able
to one-up you anymore.
The people will finally be free.
I'll make sure of it.
Just a little more patience
and like what Ivy said,
they'll all fall.
[tense music playing]
[music stops]
[cell phone ringing]
Hon?
Finally, you answered.
Are you okay? You sound nervous.
Uh…
I'm just worried about you.
Stay where you are.
My bodyguards are on their way
to pick you up.
Wait, what's happening?
Is there something wrong?
That traitor Madrigal barged
into my stag party.
I almost got killed!
That bastard. If he thinks
Jaguar can protect him, he's wrong.
Wait, what? Madrigal works for Jaguar?
[Arnaldo] Yes.
They're now in cahoots.
And I know they will do
everything to stop our wedding.
[suspenseful music playing]
[unsettling music playing]
Why don't you want to show
your face to me?
Because you might see me differently.
[gloomy piano music playing]
Where could Jepoy be?
Where did he go?
[sighs]
[clicks tongue]
Jepoy!
Jepoy, where have you been?
I haven't seen you all day.
I just walked around Ardiente.
Where exactly did you go?
I said I went to Ardiente.
-Why do you keep asking?
-What are you hiding?
-I'm not hiding anything.
-Let me see.
-Anna!
-What's this stain on your shirt?
-It's nothing.
-Come here.
Anna, that hurts! Wait!
Let me see!
[tense music playing]
Jepoy, what's that? Why are you wounded?!
Who did this to you?!
I came face-to-face with Arnaldo.
Too bad I wasn't able to kill him.
[breathes sharply]
What? Arnaldo?!
How could you be so careless, Jepoy?!
Anna, this is nothing.
-I'm fine.
-No, you're not!
What if you get caught next time?
Or worse, you get killed!
You're throwing your life away!
I won't let him catch me alive!
I'd rather shoot myself in the head, Anna!
[gloomy piano music playing]
I'll do anything to stop them
from getting married.
Jepoy, I know you're mad.
But you have to get a hold of yourself
because your anger could ruin
both your life and Ivy's plans!
[cell phone ringing]
[ringing continues]
Mm.
Ivy?
Jepoy, where are you? We need to talk.
We have to meet right now.
Okay. Where are you? I'll meet you there.
See? I think Ivy
already knows what you did.
I'm sure she's mad at you again.
I don't care if she's mad or not, Anna.
I did all this for her.
[gloomy piano music playing]
Go get some rest, okay?
I'm fine. Don't worry about me.
[gloomy piano music playing]
Wait. Hold on.
What about Raul?
[shushes]
[Julio] For years, I have watched you…
You really won't stop?
What do you want? Huh?!
-…begging…
-Why can't you stop
being unfaithful?
…pleading for his love!
But that Raul has never
had any love to give you.
Papa's right. You make me miserable, Raul!
But you know, Raul cheated
so many times, so I could--
[moans]
[dramatic music playing]
[unsettling music playing]
[Jepoy] You don't have to do that.
I'm here. We're here!
We can bring the Ardientes down!
You don't have to use yourself
as bait to catch Arnaldo!
-Jepoy.
-What?!
Diego, will you just sit around
while Ivy and Arnaldo get married?!
Jepoy. Jepoy, of all people,
shouldn't you be the one
who understands why I need
to marry Arnaldo?!
The wedding will push through.
Whether you like it or not,
it's going to happen!
[tense music playing]
[music stops]
Ivy.
You were hit?
Did you think I wouldn't find out, Jepoy?
Let me remind you, I know everything.
What are you doing?
Are you going against my plans?
You almost killed Arnaldo.
Wow, Ivy! Do you hear yourself?
I'm the one who got hit.
I barely scratched Arnaldo!
Are you still pretending?
Or do you really have feelings for him?
Have you forgotten about
what they did to Nanny Carlotta?
Have you forgotten about--
Have you forgotten
about what they did to me?!
Because everything the Ardientes did
will forever be etched in my memory, Ivy.
I didn't forget anything.
Jepoy, you have no idea
how heavy my heart feels.
How could I forget,
when every time I close my eyes,
I see Nanny Carlotta hanging by her neck?
Every time I try to sleep,
I get nightmares reminding me
of all the horrible things
they did to my parents.
Do you think I feel happy
every time I'm with the Ardientes?
I find it hard to breathe
because I want to hurt them!
I want to kill them
for everything they did to you!
So, I can never forget.
You have no idea, Jepoy--
You're right. I don't know a thing, Ivy.
Ever since I left,
you've kept me in the dark!
Was I gone that long?
You never tell me anything!
Everything I know,
I had to discover by myself!
You used to tell me all your plans.
I don't even know you anymore.
The Ivy that I knew wouldn't be
marrying that bastard Arnaldo.
The Jepoy that I knew…
would tell me all his plans.
The Jepoy that I knew
would never join forces
with that evil Jaguar.
The Jepoy that I knew wouldn't
endanger other people's lives.
The Jepoy that I knew
would consult me first
before carrying out his plan.
Fine, Ivy! Maybe I've changed.
I let my emotions control my decisions.
But I did everything for you.
You didn't do them for me.
You did them for yourself!
No, Ivy! I did all of that for you!
I let my feelings get the best of me
because I love you not just as a friend!
I love you, Ivy.
I love you so much.
I've loved you since we were kids, Ivy.
[somber music playing]
That's why I can't let you marry Arnaldo
because you will only
be miserable with him.
And I will never forgive myself
if that happens to you.
Jepoy, my life won't be miserable.
It's the lives of the Ardientes
that will be miserable.
Jepoy…
Please listen to me.
You and Anna should stay away
because I don't want you
to get dragged into my plans.
Why are you pushing me away, Ivy?
I can't leave your side!
Didn't you hear me?
I said I love you.
I love you so much, Ivy.
[somber music playing]
Jepoy, if you really love me…
you'll do what I say.
[somber music playing]
I've already lost so much.
I don't want to lose you too.
I don't care if I lose my life, Ivy.
I'll protect you until my last breath.
I love you so much, Ivy.
I'll do that for you.
You can't stop me.
[somber music playing]
[breathing sharply]
[exhales]
[Jepoy] Ever since we were kids,
you're all I have.
You're my family and my friend.
I'll protect you.
I'll never leave your side.
Whatever happens, I won't leave you.
[Ivy] You're risking your life
every day just for me.
Ivy, you don't understand.
That's not enough because I love you.
[somber music playing]
[sobbing]
[sobbing continues]
I must admit…
I enjoy the feeling of being bad.
I didn't know you were a great lover.
That's why I've made my decision.
I'll leave my father, and I'll join you.
We'll take my father down together.
You'll be the one
to make my dream come true.
So, starting today, Jaguar, you are mine,
and I am yours.
You and I will be the king
and queen of this province.
[suspenseful music playing]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[sniffles]
Jepoy, I'm right here, okay?
If you need someone to talk to.
[poignant piano music playing]
Anna…
Was I wrong to love Ivy?
[sniffles]
[Anna] It's never wrong to love.
It's just that sometimes,
some things aren't meant to be.
She does love you…
But as a friend.
Jepoy, let's just try
to be more understanding.
Because all this
isn't easy for her, right?
Right now, she needs you to support her
rather than go against her.
Anna…
[sniffles]
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
You wouldn't be the friend
we call "Jepoy the Rascal"
if you weren't stubborn.
Do you understand?
You're right, Anna.
[sniffles]
I am stubborn.
[Anna laughs]
[ice cubes clink]
[unsettling music playing]
Soon, Emilia…
Everyone will bow down to you again.
Because the real queen is so back.
-I love being back.
-[cell phone ringing]
Hmm…
Hello, Aunt Claire?
Thank goodness you answered.
I was worried about you.
I've been calling you.
I'm so sorry for not answering.
I've been very busy with Jaguar.
What did he do to you? Did he hurt you?
[chuckles]
It's the opposite, Auntie.
Jaguar pleased me.
By the way, um…
where are Papa, Raul, and Arnaldo?
Your papa and Arnaldo are at home.
I didn't tell them what happened
to you, by the way.
But Raul and Ivy Aguas are not yet here.
Huh?
That's really fishy, Aunt Claire.
But okay. I'll deal with Ivy Aguas later.
I shall be home soon, Auntie. See you.
Okay, take care.
[chuckles]
-Hi, Aunt Claire.
-Raul.
How are you? Where's Emilia?
[gloomy music playing]
She's not home yet. But she's on her way.
Weren't you with her
at Ivy's bridal shower?
Yeah. Yeah.
Where did she go?
She said she had somewhere to be.
She didn't take you with her?
Uh… I think she's with some… some friends.
[Emilia] Hi, Aunt Claire. Raul.
Hey.
[both kiss]
Hi, Auntie.
Where have you been?
Um, I went out with some friends.
We went to a bar.
Why didn't you take Aunt Claire with you?
It would've been too loud for Aunt Claire,
so I went alone.
What about you? Did you just get home?
I've been calling
-and you weren't answering.
-I was busy
with our mining shipment.
The jewelry, remember?
Oh. Okay. We were both busy,
so let's get some rest.
Wait. What's on your neck?
[tense music playing]
-Huh?
-What's on your neck?
[forced chuckle]
-An insect bite.
-An insect bite?
Hold on. Let me see.
That's not an insect bite.
Someone bit you.
Come on, Raul. So, vampires exist?
I'm not joking around. Who did that?
Do you have another man, Emilia?
Who did that?
Huh?
There's no other man, Raul.
You're the only man in my life.
And now you're lying, Emilia.
Who did that to you?
Listen to me, Emilia.
Whoever did that to you
is going to deal with me.
Who was it?
Unbelievable.
Raul, stop.
Raul…
There is no other man.
You're the only man in my life.
[suspenseful music playing]
If you want to cheat, Emilia,
go ahead and do it as much as you want.
But remember this.
You and your lover need to be careful.
Because I'm going to kill him.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Emilia] I'll go take a shower.
Grandpa, why are you still up?
[groans]
Arnaldo… Where's your bride?
I had my men pick her up.
They're on their way back here.
My question is,
where will I imprison her
until our wedding day?
[chuckles]
Good question.
[suspenseful music playing]
[gloomy music playing]
[gun clicks]
Even if I have to kill someone, Ivy…
[suspenseful music playing]
I swear you will not marry that bastard.
[Ivy sighs]
I don't know why they can't understand.
Why can't they see that I need
to push through with my plans?
Ivy, it's not like they can't understand.
They're just scared that something bad
might happen to you.
To be honest, Ivy…
I'm worried too.
I wouldn't know what I'd do
if anything happens to you.
[poignant piano music playing]
Diego, I know how deeply
concerned you are.
I'm sorry for making you
all worry so much.
But this is a risk I have to take.
It's necessary
if I want my plans to succeed.
I know.
I understand.
That's why I'm here for you.
[poignant piano music playing]
Thank you for everything, Diego.
For your support, and for all your help.
Ivy, I'm right here.
I will never get tired of helping you.
[guitar music playing]
Is this the last time we'll see
each other before your wedding?
Maybe… Maybe not.
Thank you, Diego.
Take good care of yourself, all right?
Be careful, Ivy.
["Hindi Kita Iiwan" playing]
Take care.
Thanks.
Lily. Thanks for helping me out.
["Hindi Kita Iiwan" playing]
[song fades]
-Hon.
What's happening?
I'm sorry I had my men pick you up.
It's dangerous for you to be outside.
Thank you.
You always prioritize my safety.
Of course.
In fact, Grandpa and I
decided that from tonight
until the wedding day,
you'll just stay here.
You aren't going out, okay?
Congressman, hon,
that's like locking me up.
That's exactly what it is.
It should be like this,
so no one can steal you from me.
This wedding must and will happen.
[unsettling music playing]
Okay? Yes?
We need to be alert.
Something big will happen tomorrow.
What do you mean?
[Julio] I want the perimeter
of the wedding venue
tightly secured.
If anyone starts trouble, shoot them down.
[Ivy] This town will finally be free
from the hands of the evil Ardientes.
What are you doing here?
[Jepoy] I'm going to stop the wedding,
and I'll take out whoever gets in my way.
Even you.
[Emilia] Make sure that Ivy Aguas
doesn't enter the church alive.
[theme music playing]